This is vigilante justice.
It's illegal, you know that?
Tell me, massaging you like this,
could I make a living?
Of course you can.
Then just sign the Aimin Street contract.
Turn the layoffs into transfers.
The leftover money,
wouldn't that all be our factory's profit?
Sign your name.
Sign it!
Fine, I'll sign.
Boss Long, who am I?
What?
I said, who am I?
Secretary Yu.
Let's not joke around, okay?
Which real estate company in all of Night City
doesn't know who you are?
So do you
think I'm easy to fool?
Secretary Yu, this...
What does fifty-two mean?
This fifty-two...
I suspect it's Ge Zhendong and that...
Boss Long.
Our previous cooperation
has gone pretty smoothly.
But this Aimin Street project
is more important than all the others.
If anything goes wrong with Aimin Street,
I think Night City
doesn't necessarily need the Giant Wood Group.
What do you think?
You're absolutely right.
Secretary Yu,
don't disappoint me again.
Zhu Yihai,
If you're heartless, don't blame me for being ruthless.
Excuse me,
is Mr. Zhu Yihai here?
Mr. Zhu?
We do have a Brother Zhu here.
What for?
Brother Zhu helped me the other day.
I came specifically to thank him.
No need.
How do you plan on thanking me?
Brother Zhu,
will you teach me to play pool?
No way.
I can.
Just playing is too boring.
How about we add a little sweetener?
What kind of sweetener?
Whoever wins between us
has to do one thing for the other.
How about it?
But I'd like to think you're a good kid.
Good kids shouldn't have bad intentions.
Hey,
you two,
Get a room!
What if I do have bad intentions?
Hey, Zhu Yihai,
what are you doing here?
Don't be mad, don't be mad.
How can I not be mad?
Getting handsy with someone.
I said he wouldn't do that.
I didn't bump into you, did I?
I didn't touch her.
She twisted it.
Sprained her ankle.
If you know, why ask?
Quick.
Rub it for me.
Done playing? Move it.
Others need the table.
Can you slow down?
She's injured, you know.
Forget it, forget it.
So many people in this pool hall.
People get jealous easily.
Didn't know that besides being handsome,
you also know how to care for someone.
You won the game.
So tell me, what do you want?
Don't be so serious.
I won't bite.
You're shameless.
Alright, I'll make my request then.
Don't back out.
Only dogs back out.
I want you to sing Karaoke with me.
Karaoke?
Sure.
Put on the fur coat.
Money's right here.
I can't stand Zhu Yihai's stupid face.
Hasn't Dahai always been like that?
Look at how you were acting.
I just don't want him to end up
like Dali's dad, you know?
Dali.
I didn't mean it that way.
Don't get me wrong.
Don't take it to heart.
You're right.
He's gone astray.
I gotta have a word with that woman.
Dali.
We're like a dotted line,
fading in and out in the monsoon.
So then,
what are you waiting for?
Why are you so naughty?
Could I ever be as bad as you?
I just don't get it.
Get what?
I don't get why you came looking for me.
Do you believe in fate?
I believe in orders.
What do you mean?
You wouldn't be here without a reason.
What are you really after?
Brother Hai.
Qianmei.
What are you doing here?
They...
They want to drag me off as a hostess.
Brother Hai.
Stay out of this.
This woman owes us money.
Hurry up.
Brother Hai, save me.
Move.
What are you doing?
You really getting involved?
Of course I am.
Brother Hai.
You're putting us in a tough spot.
I'm just doing my job.
Come on, brother, lighten up.
Tell you what.
Let her keep me company tonight.
After that,
I'll bring her over tomorrow, deal?
Brother Hai's a person of sentiment too.
Fine.
Wishing Brother Hai a night of passion.
All night long.
Thank you.
Thanks, brother.
Alright.
Hurry home.
Go on.
Go, go, go.
What are you looking at?
Are we drinking or what?
Let's drink.
No matter what tonight,
I'm having a drink with the big hero.
Drink this.
What are you thinking about?
I'm wondering...
who could've sent you.
Room 302 has the answer you want.
The money's right here.
Alright.
Sly as a fox.
If I weren't sharp,
I'd actually think you fell for me.
Just you wait.
As for the rest,
watch me work my magic.
My dear Jiao Jing,
tonight I come to your door.
Will you open it for me?
Who is it?
Jingjing.
Coming, coming.
Didn't I give you a key?
What's the rush?